[{"answer": "Yes, you know, at least 10 percent now.", "docId": "120822pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "How likely is it that this hurricane could build up and hit Tampa?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "That's correct.", "docId": "120822pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "And regardless of whether the eye of the storm hits Tampa, is it pretty likely that Tampa would get some pretty extreme weather anyway?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "It's going to take -- it's going to take a couple of days for me to know it.", "docId": "120822pmt", "aSentId": 80, "question": "So is it -- is it take the willies time or something a little stronger?", "qSentId": 79}, {"answer": "Yes, it might be a little bit more of the latter.", "docId": "120822pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "Or could this really bring the social issues of the right wing of the conservatives to the fore on this convention which could be damaging to Romney?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "Well, I think that in order for Romney to win, he's going to need minorities, he's going to need women, he's going to need swing states like Ohio and Pennsylvania and Florida.", "docId": "120822pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "When people hear this and see this, they don't really know what they're voting for, do they, Bill?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I can't speak for Mitt Romney and his flip-flopping.", "docId": "120822pmt", "aSentId": 182, "question": "Where's the consistency here, Amy?", "qSentId": 181}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120822pmt", "aSentId": 234, "question": "If it comes down to money buying an election, that can't be good for America democracy, can it?", "qSentId": 233}, {"answer": "Well, a couple of corrections.", "docId": "120822pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "Do you feel comfortable as a Republican that it could come down to firepower and money from super PACs?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "It's 7.8 was the --", "docId": "120822pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "It's higher than when he took office?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "Well, we saw in 2010 that voters punished this unemployment rate.", "docId": "120822pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "Are they going to punish him in November, do you think?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "Well, he's not going to step down because he's going to be a sympathetic figure for the far right within Missouri.", "docId": "120822pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "What do you make of that?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "120822pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "Or for women's rights more, isn't it?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "OK, the final record is not yet a success.", "docId": "120822pmt", "aSentId": 378, "question": "But in getting Americans back to work, Barack Obama has not been very successful, has he?", "qSentId": 377}, {"answer": "I start with a bias.", "docId": "120822pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "What is your honest assessment of his performance as president in the last four years?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "It's that sometimes he's too cool.", "docId": "120822pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "What's his biggest fault?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "It's the audience.", "docId": "120822pmt", "aSentId": 532, "question": "Do you still get as much fun out of it?", "qSentId": 531}, {"answer": "Well, the honest answer is, you saw the passion I have about politics, and I really do.", "docId": "120822pmt", "aSentId": 549, "question": "What do you say to friends of yours like mine that say to you?", "qSentId": 548}, {"answer": "I've told NBC Universal that I am going to stop.", "docId": "120822pmt", "aSentId": 567, "question": "Will you ever quit that show?", "qSentId": 566}, {"answer": "When I'm 104.", "docId": "120822pmt", "aSentId": 569, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 568}, {"answer": "That's great.", "docId": "120822pmt", "aSentId": 573, "question": "So next year?", "qSentId": 572}, {"answer": "Oh.", "docId": "120822pmt", "aSentId": 576, "question": "That's next year then?", "qSentId": 575}]